A Guide to the Correspondence of Ezra Pound and Edmund Dulac 1915-1953
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Correspondence of Ezra Pound and Edmund Dulac 1915-1953
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
5288
This collection consists of 31 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Scope and Content Information
Writing as editor of The Little Review and also from St. Elizabeth's Hospital in Washington, D.C., Pound discusses a variety of topics, including his own work. Also included are two poems, and most of the correspondence is composed in poetic and stream of consciousness style.
Contents List
- Ezra Pound to Ineffable and Terrible Substance [ca. 1915], ALS, 2 pp.
- Ezra Pound to Edmund Dulac [1916 Jun 20], APCS
- Ezra Pound to O Whong 1918 Jan 30, TLS, 1 p.
- Ezra Pound to Au pere createur 1918 Mar 16, APCS
- Ezra Pound to O august [1918] July 19, TLS, 1 p.
- Ezra Pound to Ex-Salted Pinnacle [ca. 1918], TLS, 2 pp.
- Ezra Pound to Car-Rissumus Edmundus [ca. 1918], TLS, 1 p.
- [Ezra Pound] to O Wong 1919 April 2, TL, 1 p.
- Ezra Pound to O Wong 1919 May 3, APCS
- Ezra Pound to Cher Edmond [ca. 1920], TL, 1 p.
- Ezra Pound to Cher M- [ca. 1920], ALS, 1 p.
- Ezra Pound to Frater casissime nostri [1925] Apr 22, TLS, 2 pp.
- Ezra Pound to O Wong 1925 Dec 26, ALS, 1 p.
- [Ezra Pound] to [Edmund Dulac] [ca. 1925], TN, frag.
- Ezra Pound to Hi Wong 1926 Nov 28, TLS, 1 p.
- Ezra Pound to My Dear Edmond 1927 Mar 12, TLS, 2 pp.
- Ezra Pound to O Wong [1935] May 4, TLS, 2 pp.
- Ezra Pound to Oh Whonggg [1935] Jun 20, TLS, 2 pp.
- Ezra Pound to Hhoo hWong [1935] Dec 28, TLS, 1 p.
- Ezra Pound to O Wong 1937 Jan 17, TLS, 1 p.
- Ezra Pound to Waaaal... [1938] Nov 21, TLS, 2 pp.
- Ezra Pound to Waal [1950 Jul 15], ALS, 2 pp.
- Ezra Pound to [Edmund Dulac] 1950 Oct 7, ALS, 1 p.
- Ezra Pound to [Edmund Dulac] 1951 Jan 10, ALS, 2 p.
- E.P. to Ex-salted Pinackle 1951 Mar 17, TL carbon, 2 pp.
- Ezra Pound to Edmund Dulac [1951 Apr 2], APCS
- Ezra Pound to O Wong [1951] Dec, ALS, 1 p.
- Ezra Pound to O Wong 1952 Apr 28, ALS, 3 pp.
- Ezra Pound to [Edmund Dulac] n.d., TL, 1 p.
- Ezra Pound to [Edmund Dulac] n.d., TL, 1 p.
- Ezra Pound to [Edmund Dulac] n.d., ALS, 2 p.